addictivetext.com 2014-11-23

# Privacy Policy | Antification

Our business is focused on creating the best publication for our clients and educating people about the need to assure their own financial security and ways to do that. Antification.com is the site to which this privacy policy applies.

You can access our website homepage and browse our site without disclosing personal information. If you request information from our website: We will use the information you provide to assist in getting you the information requested, to make specific recommendations, to enhance our understanding of client needs, and improve our marketing effectiveness.

We will not distribute or share your information with outside companies except the information needed should you request or purchase another company’s product from our site, to properly credit referral sources, or for billing purposes directly related to a client’s account. Your personal data will not be disclosed to government institutions or authorities except if compelled by law.

If you give us permission to email you, when we do it’s about something we think is great (not just good). However, you can unsubscribe at any time by clicking the link stating such at the bottom of any of our emails. We don’t want to be sending things you don’t want any more than we want to get offers for prescription drugs from Quebec. We don’t knowingly collect personal data from children. Not only is that the law in most nations, most of them don’t even invest in financial publications or business tools anyway.

Our website improves based on analytical usage data. This non-personal data collected via cookies or other methods helps us understand what sections of our site people spend the most time on and what areas are the most useful to our visitors and clients. Our website does provide the opportunity for visitors and clients to use a secure transmission method to send information. All order forms require secure transmission.

Third parties may use cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to collect or receive information from this website and use that information to provide measurement services and target ads. The use of cookies by third parties can be disabled in your browser settings. You can opt out of customized ads in Facebook [on this page](http://www.facebook.com/ads/website_custom_audiences/).

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data entered during the order process from: unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, unlawful destruction, and accidental loss. All our employees and data and payment processors who have access to, or are associated with, the processing of personal data are contractually obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors’ personal data and are subject to monitoring.

We’ll provide you with a copy of the personal data which we keep about you if requested and you may update/change/delete the information. The exemption is if you’re a client. We would delete you from any other research database or testimonial record; but we’ll still keep record of your purchase. Without exception we require proof of your identity before releasing your records.

Our website and emails can include links to third party sites (including HMRC, the IRS, other publishers, vendors, and various charities). They have their own privacy policies and we don’t control anything that happens on their websites good, bad, or otherwise. So surf away from our site at your own peril.

If you have an enquiry or any concern about our privacy policy, website, or communications, please contact us via email, support@addictivetext.com. You may send physical mail to: The TransformX Consortium, 78 Anne Boleyn’s Walk, Cheam, SM3 8DF, United Kingdom.
